# Vladyslav Nasadyk

t.empire228@gmail.com +380664074012 Ivano-Frankivsk

#### Summary

2+ years of experience in Front-End, Design web-pages, Writing technical task, Development of user interfaces, Creating, programming web-sites, Leading the team, Fix bugs, Technology stack selection. I am responsible, proactive, stress-resistant, sociable, honest. My strengths: good management and leadership skills, customer focus, systematic thinking, positive attitude. It is very important for me to feel respect among employees. I like tasks in which you need to show individual creativity. I work best in a team, I value honesty and work ethic.

#### **Experience**

## GrowsUpSolutions

Junior Front End Developer 09/2020 - 02/2021

Development of frontend projects Designing user interfaces Cross-browser and adaptive layout Product support

#### CleverStaff

Front End Developer • Kyiv 02/2021 - 11/2021

Custom program development - CleverStaff Fix bugs Programming Chrome Extension - Plugin CleverStaff Refactoring someone else's code

#### CleverStaff

Tech Lead/Developer • Kyiv 11/2021 - Present

Team support and leadership Writing documentation Carrying out onboarding Estimation of term of works Technology stack selection

#### Skills

• HTML

• JADE

• SCSS (Sassy Cascading Style Sheets)

JavaScript

TypeScript

Redux

AngularJS

AJAX

· MySQL

· Unit Testing

• SPA

WebPack

• SDLC

KANBAN

PUG

• CSS

LESS

ES6

ReactJS

Angular

HandleBars

• GIT

MongoDB

REST

Bootstrap

GULP

SCRUM

· MaterialUI

#### **Education**

## **Tlumach College LNAU**

Finance, banking and insurance • Tlumach

06/2018

# King Danylo University

Software Engineering • Ivano-Frankivsk

### Languages

• English - Intermidiate

• Ukrainian - Native